Mark Winston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Research records, 1970 - 2014; F-174-4; 3.72 m of textual records 19 MB of textual records (electronic) 87 photographs 3,095 photographs: col. slides 40 sound recordings 14 moving images 2 multiple media documents; General note locations of special media: * Textual records in electronic form are l
  - Conferences and presentations, 1981 - 2008; F-174-4-5; 31.4 cm of textual records 19 MB of textual records (electronic) 16 photographs (electronic) 477 photographs: col. slides
    - Ireland, 2003; F-174-4-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
    - Ireland photos (JPEG images on CD), 2003; F-174-4-5-0-24 (Cd box 174-80, Optical disc: cd OBJ-1073)
      Contains 16 digital photographs (jpeg format).
    - Conferences/presentations, 2004; F-174-4-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
    - Conferences/presentations, 2005; F-174-4-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
    - IUSSI presentation, 2006; F-174-4-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
    - Dr Shafik Dharamsi, UBC - Social Responsibility Panel; World Urban Forum (WUF) panel, 2006; F-174-4-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Celebration of Writing Week: Houston, 2008; F-174-4-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Bacon and Eggheads II, 2008; F-174-4-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Killer Bee - UBC Talk, 16 September 1981, Institute of Animal Ecology, F-174-4-5-0-31; 54 photographs: col. slides 1 textual record (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Queen over wintering & banking, Part 1 from package talk,..., 1985; F-174-4-5-0-32; 124 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Why bees do it when: Temporal Caste Structure in..., 1985; F-174-4-5-0-33; 73 photographs: col. slides 1 textual record; The archivist photocopied the original, annotated metal carrying case lid and included the copy on the file. Also included are original labels from the lid. (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Seasonal Management and How to Inspect a Hive, 1985; F-174-4-5-0-34; 65 photographs: col. slides 1 textual record (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - The Essence of Royalty: Honey Bee Queen Pheromone - research talk, 1992; F-174-4-5-0-35; 83 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
      Slides were originally housed in a carousel. The archivist re-housed the slides into sleeves in the identical order in which they were found. The slides before the gap in the sleeves were housed in the carousel tray, while the slides after the gap in the sleeves were found bundled together in the centre of the tray.
    - Of Mites and Bees, 1998; F-174-4-5-0-36; 78 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
  - Audio-visual and photographic materials, [197-?] - 2006; F-174-4-6; 14 moving images 2,409 photographs: col. slides
    A number of the slides in this sub-series were in individual sleeves annotated by topic, but the sleeves were in no apparent order. Some sleeves were grouped into binders by topic. As such, once all sleeves were foldered, the entire sub-series of files was loosely arranged around common topics identified from the annotations and binder topics. The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
    - Killer Bees ... Fact or Fantasy, 1977; F-174-4-6-0-0-1 (Film reel OBJ-2740)
      Moving images
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item85.
    - The Leading Edge II no. 13, [199-?]; F-174-4-6-0-0-2; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2406)
      OBJ-2406 also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item69.
    - Science Council Awards Show, [199-?]; F-174-4-6-0-0-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2407)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item70.
    - Frontiers of Discovery, 1992; F-174-4-6-0-0-4; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2408)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item71.
    - Bee Beards (BCTV and SFU IMC footage), 1993; F-174-4-6-0-0-5 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2409)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item72.
    - Spiritual Needs and Religious Practices of the Jewish Patient, 1996; F-174-4-6-0-0-6; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2410)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item73.
    - Manning Innovation Awards - Winner Profiles, November 1997; F-174-4-6-0-0-7; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2411)
      OBJ-2411 also available in .mkv format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item74.
    - Television interviews, 1986-[200?] (various), F-174-4-6-0-0-8; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2405)
      .mkv file also available in .mp4 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item68.
    - NSERC Michael Smith Award Promotional Video, [200-?]; F-174-4-6-0-0-9; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2412)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item75.
    - Vancouver Institute presentation, 2000; F-174-4-6-0-0-10; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2413)
      Item is a VHS recording of a Vancouver Institute lecture given by Dr. Mark Winston on February 12, 2000. Lecture was co-sponsored by Simon Fraser University.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item76.
    - The Bee Talkers demo, February 2003; F-174-4-6-0-0-11; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2414)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item77.
    - Studio 4 with Fanny Kiefer interview, July 4, 2003; F-174-4-6-0-0-12; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2415)
      Kiefer, Fanny; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item78.
    - The Nature of Things - Beetalkers David Denning [silent footage of bees], 2005; F-174-4-6-0-0-13; 2 videocassettes 2 .mkv files (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2416, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2417)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Denning, David; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .mkv files also available in .mp4 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item83, F-174-item84.
    - The Nature of Things - Beetalkers, 2006; F-174-4-6-0-0-14 (Optical disc: dvd OBJ-2418, Optical disc: dvd-r OBJ-4100)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Suzuki, David; Moving images
      Duration: 0
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item79.
    - Africanized: general, research and equipment, 1975 - 1981; F-174-4-6-0-1; 123 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Africanized bees, 1976 - 1983; F-174-4-6-0-2; 38 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Africanized: general, 1974 - 1977; F-174-4-6-0-3; 38 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Data, pheromones, vol. 1, [ca. 1978] - 1996; F-174-4-6-0-4; 226 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Data, pheromones, vol. 2, [ca. 1978] - 1996; F-174-4-6-0-5; 211 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Data, pheromones, vol. 3, [ca. 1978] - 1996; F-174-4-6-0-6; 177 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Nature Wars, data, disease, blueberry pollination, 1991 - 1998; F-174-4-6-0-7; 143 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Queens and queen rearing, drones, behavior,..., 1972 - 1994; F-174-4-6-0-8; 184 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Queens and drones, queens and queen rearing, [ca. 1988] - 1994; F-174-4-6-0-9; 47 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-97)
    - Management: Packages, Wintering, Late Winter, Early Spring,..., 1977 - 1983, 1994 - 1996; F-174-4-6-0-10; 138 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Management, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-11; 42 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Management: Mid-spring and swarm control, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-12; 20 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Packages, [198-]; F-174-4-6-0-13; 34 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Diseases, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-14; 45 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Anatomy, [197-?] - [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-15; 40 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Anatomy and development, 1989 - 1994; F-174-4-6-0-16; 33 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Research and equipment 1, 1976 - 1977; F-174-4-6-0-17; 15 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Research and equipment 2, 1976 - [ca. 1983]; F-174-4-6-0-18; 20 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Nests, 1976 - 1977; F-174-4-6-0-19; 20 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Nests, 1976 - 1983; F-174-4-6-0-20; 63 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Field research - Mexico, Venezuela, Brazil, 1977 - 1980; F-174-4-6-0-21; 7 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Sequence of images - person in beekeeping suit inspecting bee boxes, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-22; 36 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Bees - close-ups, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-23; 19 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Bees & Beekeeping, 1983 - "Bees" #32-38, 39-57, 1-19, 58-76, 77-95..., F-174-4-6-0-24; 96 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
      Carefoot, Elizabeth; Photographic materials
    - Bee boxes and person in beekeeping suit, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-25; 20 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Bees - illustrations, 1982 - 1983; F-174-4-6-0-26; 19 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Prog 2 - bee close-ups and illustrations, [198-?]; F-174-4-6-0-27; 40 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Various - beekeeping, bee boxes, swarms, close-ups, illustrations, Peru, 1977 - 1989; F-174-4-6-0-28; 276 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-98)
    - Field research in marine biology, entomology, hermit crabs - French Guiana, Peru, etc., 1973 - 1977; F-174-4-6-0-29; 160 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - small 174-99)
    - Field research - marine biology, 1974; F-174-4-6-0-30; 79 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - small 174-99)
- Grant and funding records, 1980 - 2007; F-174-5; 65.6 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Mark Winston's research grants while at Simon Fraser University and includes applications and correspondence with his graduate students and local, provincial, and national granting agencies such as SFU Special Research Projects, the BC Honey Producers Association, the Science Council of BC, Killam Foundation, NSERC, the National Research Council, Agriculture Canada, the EJLB Foundation, and companies including Monsanto and Bayer.
  Records include correspondence, reports, budget and financial working papers, applications and contracts, and brochures.
  British Columbia Honey Producers Association; Science Council of B.C.; Killam Foundation; Natural Science and Engineering Research Council; National Research Council; Canada. Agriculture Canada; Monsanto Company; Bayer AG
  - NSERC grants, 1980 - 1983; F-174-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - National Research Council contract on pollination/pesticides, 1981 - 1984; F-174-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Science Council of British Columbia, vol. 1, 1982 - 1985; F-174-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Science Council of British Columbia, vol. 2, 1982 - 1985; F-174-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Grants - NSERC undergrad, grad, post doc, 1982 - 1996; F-174-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Science Council of British Columbia: Okanogan Valley pollination, 1983 - 1984; F-174-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - NSERC grants, 1983 - 1985; F-174-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Science Council of British Columbia, 1984 - 1985; F-174-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - Agriculture Canada grants, 1984 - 1988; F-174-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - NSERC Strategic Grants Program, 1985 - 1990; F-174-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-44)
  - NSERC grants, 1986 - 1988; F-174-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - ARDSA, 1986 - 1990; F-174-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - SFU Special Research Projects: Queen substance, 1987; F-174-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - NSERC: Schmid-Hempel grant, 1987 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Science Council of British Columbia, 1988 - 1989; F-174-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - ARDSA reports, vol. 1, 1988 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - ARDSA reports, vol. 2, 1988 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Wright Institute Award, 1988 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - NSERC grants, 1989 - 1990; F-174-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Science Council of British Columbia: Queen Bee Pheromone year 2, 1989 - 1990; F-174-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - NSERC equipment, 1989 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Science Council of BC: G.R.E.A.T. Award - K. Naumann, 1989 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - SFU Special Research Projects, 1990; F-174-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Cranberry proposal, 1990; F-174-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Science and Technology Research Fund, 1990 - 1991; F-174-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-45)
  - Science Council of British Columbia: Queen Bee Pheromone year 3, 1990 - 1992; F-174-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - Canadian Agri-Food Development Iniative, 1991 - 1994; F-174-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - NSERC Strategic Grants Program, 1991 - 1997; F-174-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - NSERC, 1992 - 1994; F-174-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - KOPPERT application, 1993; F-174-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - Killam, 1994; F-174-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - Neuromodulator grant, 1994 - 1997; F-174-5-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - Applied Research Partnerships Program (Neem extracts), 1995; F-174-5-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - Pollination grants, 1995 - 1998; F-174-5-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - NSERC, 1995 - 1999; F-174-5-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - BARD proposal, 1996; F-174-5-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - NSERC: Varroa grant, vol. 1, 1996 - 2001; F-174-5-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 174-46)
  - NSERC: Varroa grant, vol. 2, 1996 - 2001; F-174-5-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Agri-Food Innovation Fund: Danielle, 1997; F-174-5-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Agri-Food Innovation Fund: Lynn, 1997; F-174-5-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Killam, 1997 - 1998; F-174-5-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Agri-Food Innovation Fund, 1997 - 1999; F-174-5-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Agri-Food general, 1997 - 2000; F-174-5-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Killam, 1998 - 2002; F-174-5-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Alice and Desiree proposals, 1999 - 2001; F-174-5-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - EJLB Foundation, 1999 - 2002; F-174-5-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - NSERC, 1999 - 2003; F-174-5-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Greenhouse grant, vol. 1, 1999 - 2003; F-174-5-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 174-47)
  - Greenhouse grant, vol. 2, 1999 - 2003; F-174-5-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Gene behaviour pheromone grants, 2000 - 2001; F-174-5-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Lora: BCHPA, 2001; F-174-5-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Lora: Alberta Agricultural Research Institute, 2001 - 2002; F-174-5-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Lora Morandin grants, 2001 - 2002; F-174-5-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Lora: Monsanto, 2001 - 2003; F-174-5-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Lora: Bayer, 2001 - 2004; F-174-5-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - NSERC grants, 2003 - 2004; F-174-5-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
  - Pollinators - partners, vol. 1, 2003 - 2004; F-174-5-0-0-57 (Archival box - small 174-78)
  - Pollinators - partners, vol. 2, 2003 - 2004; F-174-5-0-0-58 (Archival box - small 174-78)
  - Pollinators - NSERC, vol. 1, 2002 - 2007; F-174-5-0-0-59 (Archival box - small 174-78)
  - Pollinators - NSERC, vol. 2, 2002 - 2007; F-174-5-0-0-60 (Archival box - small 174-78)
  - SSHRC grants, 2005 - 2006; F-174-5-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
  - EJLB Foundation, 2004 - 2005; F-174-5-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
- Consulting records, 1981 - 2010; F-174-6; 55.7 cm of textual records 3 videocassettes; Physical description: includes 3 VHS videocassettes and 3 digital access copies.
  Series consists of records relating to Mark Winston's role as an expert in the field of apiculture and includes correspondence with law firms, businesses, the news media, and work with film and television production companies reviewing scripts and "bee wrangling" on set. Series also consists of records relating to Winston's role as an expert in dialogue, facilitation, and leadership for various businesses, governments, and NGOs. Of particular note is his extensive consulting work with Action Canada.
  Records include correspondence, contracts and invoices, reports, scripts and storyboards, working papers, presentation notes, and audio-visual materials.
  Series is arranged into 2 sub-series:
  1. Apiculture
  2. Dialogue and facilitation
  Action Canada; Free the Children; Lifespeak
  Some files in this series are restricted. Please see the file list for this series and consult the archivist for more details.
  Access to the moving images is restricted for preservation reasons due to the fragility of the storage medium (VHS videocassettes). Access is provided via digitized access copies. Please consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing these records.
  - Apiculture, 1981 - 2010; F-174-6-1; 20.4 cm of textual records 3 videocassettes 3 .mkv files
    Some files in this sub-series are restricted. Please see the file list and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Malaspina Apiculture Advisory Committee, 1981 - 1984; F-174-6-1-0-1; F-174-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
      Malaspina Apiculture Advisory Committee; Textual records
    - CBC, 1984; F-174-6-1-0-2; F-174-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Textual records
      - Beachcombers - Some bees sting parts 1 and 2, 1984; F-174-6-1-0-2-1; F-174-6-0-0-2-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2419)
        Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
        .mkv file also available in .mp4 file.
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item80.
    - Science World, 1989 - 2004; F-174-6-1-0-3; F-174-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
      Science World; Textual records
    - Watson Goepel Maledy Barristers and Solicitors, 1993 - 1994; F-174-6-1-0-4; F-174-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-48)
      Watson Goepel Maledy Barristers and Solicitors; Textual records
    - Scholastic/Magic Bus, 1995 - 1996; F-174-6-1-0-5; F-174-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Holocrafts, 1996; F-174-6-1-0-6; F-174-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Rudd: WCB Campbell, 1996; F-174-6-1-0-7; F-174-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - X-Files, 1996; F-174-6-1-0-8; F-174-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Marshall and Lamperson Lawyers and Notaries, 1997 - 2004; F-174-6-1-0-9; F-174-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      Marshall and Lamperson Lawyers and Notaries; Textual records
    - Mason Bee consulting, 1999; F-174-6-1-0-10; F-174-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - First Wave, 1999; F-174-6-1-0-11; F-174-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      - First Wave / Planet Education, 1999; F-174-6-1-0-11-1; F-174-6-0-0-11-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mkv file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2420)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item81.
    - Great Northern Productions, 1999 - 2001; F-174-6-1-0-12; F-174-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      Great Northern Productions; Textual records
    - Gibeau [Honey Bee Centre], 1999 - 2004; F-174-6-1-0-13; F-174-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Creative Animal Talent "Say It Isn't So", 2000; F-174-6-1-0-14; F-174-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Killer Bees, 2000 - 2003; F-174-6-1-0-15; F-174-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Frank O'Cone, 2001; F-174-6-1-0-16; F-174-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
    - Tigress Productions, 2001 - 2002; F-174-6-1-0-17; F-174-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      Tigress Productions; Textual records
    - Smallville, 2002; F-174-6-1-0-18; F-174-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      - Smallville, May 2002; F-174-6-1-0-18-1; F-174-6-0-0-18-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2421)
        Item is a video recording of a television broadcast of "Drone," episode 18, season one of Smallville, aired on Global TV in 2002.
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item82.
    - Canadian Biotechnology Advisory Committee, 2002 - 2003; F-174-6-1-0-19; F-174-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-49)
      Canadian Biotechnology Advisory Committee; Textual records
    - USDA Farm Report, 2005 - 2006; F-174-6-1-0-20; F-174-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
      United States. Department of Agriculture; Textual records
    - Whitlaw Twinning, 2010; F-174-6-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Borden Ladner Gervais LLP, 2009; F-174-6-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Mercer, Rick, 2007 - 2008; F-174-6-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
  - Dialogue and facilitation, 2002 - 2009; F-174-6-2; 35.3 cm of textual records
    Files or items in this sub-series may contain personal or confidential information. Those marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply.
    - Potential consulting, 2008 - 2009; F-174-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Biofuels - sustainability workshop and advisory committee, 2008 - 2009; F-174-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - BCIT - Faculty and Staff Association Summit on Research, 2009; F-174-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Free the Children, 2006 - 2008; F-174-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Lifespeak, 2007; F-174-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
    - Action Canada: general, 2002 - 2008; F-174-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada 2007 - 2008, 2006 - 2008; F-174-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada Vancouver 2007/2008 - working conference, F-174-6-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada Ottawa 2007/2008 - working conference, F-174-6-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada Quebec and Toronto 2007/2008 - working conferences, F-174-6-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada op-ed 2007/2008, F-174-6-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada 2006/2007, F-174-6-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-86)